http://www.tmelectronics.com/company/privacy.cfm

Home | Contact TME | Resources | Company
Testing 101
Overview
Why is Testing Important?
Subjects Covered
Part 1: Device and Product Integrity
Part 2: Package Testing
Part Three:
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register for Testing 101, fill out the RMA request or the Contact Us form.
When requesting a quote or additional information on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
a)      To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
b)      To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
c)       To send periodic emails
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  If you would like to opt-out of any periodic emails, please contact webmaster@tmelectronics.com and simply state “opt-out” or “remove from mailing list”.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your PCI compliance authority.
[+] Share
Email this page >
Copyright 2020 TM Electronics, Inc
Contact TME
68 Barnum Road, Devens, MA 01434-3508Tel: (978) 772-0970 | Fax: (978) 772-2048
Privacy Policy |
Site Map
Privacy Policy | TM Electronics
online privacy policy
Information about TM Electronics online privacy policy.
